

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991

E-mail: hello@naushikha.com

Website: naushikha.com

COMPUTER ENTHUSIAST

PROFILE

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with nearly 3 years of cumulative industrial experience in various fields. Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

PLAYTESTER

Arimac (Jan 2021 >>)

Testing and evaluating of Android mobile games.

VIRTUAL INTERN

Nestlé (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

• Researching about localization for the supply-chain division.

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System installation and administration
- Hardware and networking

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Voigue (Dec 2017 - Jan 2018)

• Support team services to handle Daraz.lk's excess user traffic during christmas.

INTERN

Third Space Global (Dec 2016 - Jan 2017)

 Online tutoring mathematics for school children stationed in the UK.

SKILLS

- Linux
- Networking
- System administration
- Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability

EDUCATION

BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

0/L. A/L

Ananda College, Colombo 10. (2003 - 2016)

